Okay so hello everyone in this video as you can see that I have created this beautiful
wait one second half this beautiful navbar component as well as the login component here
so login page item so you can copy all these styles okay so you can copy all these styles
I have paste it inside of this style files beginners login page.txt navbar.txt and signup.txt
whatever you can just copy that and use that as a beginner files okay so this is the update
and also the thing is that you need to make some manual change inside of this login page
and home page and navbar page okay so if I style everything here it will be quite some
boring so that's why I have taken this and also like use this okay so you have to install
some packages like react icons you know to use the icons somewhat they are used here okay
like this fi messages square and this link is important from the react router dome so now
if you navigate to the different pages like it is the login page right and for the home
page so if you go to the home then you will see this and if you go in the signup then
you will going to see that and sorry login okay so if you go to the login you will see
the login page similarly for the signup page you will see the signup I will keep on adding
all those styles okay